Whatcha gonna do?
Bad Boys is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Michael Bay.
Marcus Burnett is a henpecked family man.
Mike Lowrey is a footloose and fancy free ladies' man.
Both Miami policemen, they have 72 hours to reclaim a consignment
of drugs stolen from under their station's nose.
To complicate matters, in order to get the assistance of the sole
witness to a murder, they have to pretend to be each other.
Mike Lowrey, played by Will Smith.
Marcus Burnett, played by Martin Lawrence.
Julie Mott, played by Téa Leoni.
Fouchet, played by Tchéky Karyo.
Captain Howard, played by Joe Pantoliano.
Theresa Burnett, played by Theresa Randle.
Bad Boys is a 1995 American action comedy film, directed by Michael Bay in his feature
directorial debut, and produced by Don Simpson and Jerry Bruckheimer.
The film stars Martin Lawrence and Will Smith as Marcus Burnett and Mike Lowrey, two Miami narcotics detectives who are investigating $100
million worth of stolen packs of heroin and must also protect a woman from a drug dealer after she witnessed a key murder.
The film was released on April 7, 1995, by Columbia Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and was commercially successful, grossing $141 million, and spawning
three sequels: Bad Boys II (2003), Bad Boys for Life (2020), and Bad Boys: Ride or Die (2024).
The film explores themes of miami, florida, mexican standoff,
male friendship, witness protection, stripper.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.